onovskiye Peacekeepers will patrol
онов ские Миротворцы будут патрулировать
this
вот эту
kilometer of the Russian Federation Yes,
километровой Российской Федерации Да
to demarcate Russia and NATO that's
чтобы разграничить Россию и НАТО вот и
all And you too
всё А вы тоже
words Good evening Hello
слова Добрый вечер Здравствуйте Вы
Where are you from DPR Donetsk People's Republic
откуда ДНР Донецкая народная республика
Cool I come from Makeyevka And
Прикольно я родом из Макеевки А ты
where are you from Donetsk
откуда Донецк
early were you from Donetsk or are you in
ран ты из Донецка родом или сейчас в
Donetsk now  just
Донецке просто
alive now I live in Donetsk And where
жив сейчас я живу в Донецке А откуда
are you from Donetsk I understood How old are you
родом из Донецка понял Сколько тебе лет
19 cool Super then you are full already in
19 прикольно Супер то ты полно тие уже
short in the DPR like got yes Or already in
короче в ДНР типа получил да Или уже в
Russia someone passport
России кого паспорт
Well I got a passport in the nineteenth
Да ну я получил паспорт в девятнадцатом
year I got a Russian passport I understood
году я получил российский паспорт понял
cool  Listen, here's a question, how did
прикольно Слушай а вот такой вопрос как
you watch it, that it seems like they started their own
там вас смотрел что вроде как бы сво
to protect Donetsk,
начали чтобы защитить Донецк до сих пор
something even worse is still shelling
что-то ещё хуже обстреливает
everything, honestly, it
всё честно мне это
really doesn't matter to me, whose Donetsk it will be, so
деле без разни чей будет Донецк вот
that this ends,
чтобы это закончилось
honestly, every
чест каждый
day,
день
Sheillo I  not from Ukraine I just
Шей лло Я не из Украины Я просто
support Ukraine I am from Rostov
поддерживаю Украину я родом из Ростова
But I have been living in California for 18 years just
Но живу в Калифорнии уже 18 лет просто
in 2 years
через 2 года
twentieth what and flag Why
двадцатому что а флаг Почему украинский
is there a Ukrainian flag there I installed a VPN so that
там флаг стоит это я ставил VPN чтобы
I would come across Ukrainians Because that's how I am an
мне попадались украинцы Потому что так я
American flag and it gives me
американский флаг и оно мне даёт
all sorts of Americans And I wanted to talk
американцев всяких А я хотел поговорить
to Ukrainians and installed a VPN Ukraine Well,
с украинцами и поставил VPN Украина Ну у
I have a Russian flag Yes, you have
меня же флаг руски стоит Да у тебя
Russia  it's worth it,
Россия стоит
most of them are
попадаются большинство попадаются
Ukrainians, but sometimes Russians fly out. It's
украинцы но иногда вылетают
just that I was
россияне Просто у меня вот нас в
pushed, so to speak, face down into the dirt, everyone,
толкнули так сказать лицом в грязь всех
I seem to have a Russian flag. Yes, I go in, let's
вот меня вроде флаг русский Да я захожу
say,
вот допустим
Ukraine, they don't even know who they are. And from where they
Укра они даже не знают кто И откуда уже
immediately draw
сразу делают
conclusions, it's very upsetting that people have become
выводы очень огорчает то что люди стали
angry here In any situation remain
злыми вот В любо ситуации оставаться
human Vigo
человеком Виго
Well here you understand here the thing is
Ну тут такое понимаешь тут дело в том
that look now this I voted for Trump
что смотри сейчас вот этот Я за трампа
By the way yes because
Кстати голосовал да потому что ну
well Handsome Handsome Trump I hope he will
Красавчик Красавчик Трамп Я надеюсь он
now quickly he already said that like
сейчас быстро он уже ж сказал что типа
yes Russia should withdraw troops from
да Россия должна вывести войска из
Ukraine And then there will be a restoration of
Украины Да и тогда будет восстановление
peace, in short, he has now adopted a Decree there,
мира короче он сейчас там принял Указ то
what he said there is that there
что там он сказал то что там в Америке
will be only two generals in America, that is, men
будет только два генера то есть мужчины
and a woman, that is, Listen, wait. That is,
и женщина то есть Слушай подожди То есть
you are now in the DPR under some kind of
ты сейчас в ДНР под какими-то ракетами
you sit with rockets and worry how many
сидишь и переживаешь сколько там
genders there are in America
гендеров в Америке у
we don't have this I just generalize that
нас нет это я просто обобщают то что
Trump Well unlike Biden at least with
Трамп Ну в отличие от байдена хотя бы с
brains
мозгами
it's cool when Biden was elected there
прикольно когда байдена выбирали там же
in fact there too everything
по сути там тоже чуть-чуть не
was a little bit fabricated there was a yoke there something  they
сфабриковано всё было иго там что-то
took off I don't remember what happened those how many years
сняли я не помню что было те сколько лет
were there when Biden was
было когда байдена
elected I think or 14 Yes I'm 19 now
выбрали вроде или 14 Да у меня 19 сейчас
how many have we been ruled for 4 years I understand that's how it
сколько нам 4 года правил понял так
turns out look And what do you know about America in general
получается смотри А что вы вообще знаете
m well America now has a
м ну Америка сейчас имеет
democratic political system
демократический политический строй по
essentially capitalism there
сути капитализм там
and  the country fights racism quite
а страна борется с расизмом довольно
very successfully that is there you don't
очень ну успешно то есть там ты не
apply you won't say here you
подаёшь не скажешь вот ты
That is you will say you can easily
То есть ты скажешь тебя могут спокойно
go and write a statement
пойти заявление
Here Well what else do I
написать Вот Ну что я ещё
know And what is your standard of living now in the
знаю А как у вас сейчас уровень жизни в
DPR there
ДНР там работа
is work well now there is a program  Russian
есть ну сейчас там программа российская
is, that is, it offers there. Here are those who
есть то есть там предлагает Вот кто вот
live in the DPR, so that they can go there.
в ДНР живёт чтобы они это ездили
There in the Belgorod region, there they can work
Там в Белогородской области там работать
in factories, there are some
на заводы там какие-то
anyway, let's say, there are  work
всё равно вот допустим вот есть работа
there anyway, there is also a city there,
вот там же всё равно тоже свой город
there are housing and communal services needs, a store there anyway, I guess.
есть там нужды ЖКХ магазин там всёравно
Earlier. Earlier, people in Donetsk
поди Раньше Раньше люди в Донецке
worked in Donetsk. And now they
работали в Донецке А теперь их
are sent to work in Belgorod. Well, there
отправляют работать в Белгород Ну там же
now it is considered there, there
сейчас он считается там референдум же
was a referendum, it is considered part of Russia,
прошёл се считается как вот часть России
that is.  yes but I mean that there is
то есть да но имею в виду что в Донецке
no work in Donetsk that you only need to go to Belgrade
нет работы что только в Белград нужно
to earn money Well look now
ехать на заработки Ну смотрите сейчас
let's say there is Donetsk
вот допустим там же Донецк это что там
there are
там
coal mines steel making that is
угольные Шахты стале варение то есть
metallurgy now there well it's all in
металлургия сейчас там ну это всё в
decline And
упадке А
why Well because there is a war  there goes
почему Ну потому что Война идёт там
most of the factories
большую часть заводов
were bombed Yes and what do people think what do people
разбомбили Да а что люди думают что люди
in the DPR think about
в ДНР думают об этом
all this
всём
Well I think that the post is over it doesn't
Ну я думаю что пост закончилось вот без
matter Who will win To
разницы Вот кто победит Чтобы побыстрее
finish everything faster Well they are afraid look Well for
всё закончи Ну они боятся смотри Ну
example when I meet some
например я когда встречаю некоторых
people from the DPR they say  that they are afraid that
людей из ДНР они говорят что боятся что
some Banderites will come there you
там бандеровцы какие-то придут их вы ой
oh Well, that's all that too. The
Ну это тоже вот это всё Вот машина
propaganda machine is working right now, that's
пропаганды сейчас вот работает тоже вот
actually right now  Propaganda comes from all
на самом деле сейчас Пропаганда со всех
sides, that is, Russian In Russia
сторон идёт то есть Российская В России
they say that only Banderites
говорят то что там одни бандеровцы вот
live there Although my guys
живут Хотя вот у меня вот пацаны тоже
also live in the DPR, both Russians and Ukrainians, that's
тоже и русские и украинцы живут в ДНР
right
правильно
Yeah That is, I haven't seen them
Угу То есть я вот не видел чтобы они там
shouting there, that is, such  there wasn't
кричали там ля то есть такого вот не
there there aren't any there like
Вот не есть там вот по типу самой
some MAZs here all this well damn it's
какие-то МАЗов Вот это всё ну блин тоже
all so far-fetched that is here
всё так за уши вытянуто то есть вот
Russian
Российская
Propaganda and in Russia there are also these
Пропаганда и в России там же тоже эти
Russian marches held here all this is there
русские марши проводятся Вот это всё там
also
тоже
there Neo-Nazi raids  there for non-
там Нео нацистские рейды там по
Russians there for Tajiks remember everywhere
нерусским там по таджикам пом везде есть
there is in its own
вот в своя
good let's say here is a Ukrainian I understand
хоро вот допустим вот украинца я понимаю
why here is Russian Well because well the
почему вот вот русским Ну потому что ну
situation is such I am not bad in relation I
ситуация такая я не плохо отно я
understand perfectly well that as And I Well
прекрасно понимаю что как А я Ну
I remain a human being so I don't blame anyone
я человеком остаюсь вот я никого не виню
That  there are all normal people That is,
То есть все люди нормальные То есть
you can understand everyone I will not say never
можно всех понять я вот не скажу никогда
in life Ukraine is to blame itself
в жизни Укра пото сама рана виновата
That is, it is clear that these are the paths they
Вот то есть понятно что вот пути они у
have, both of them Zelensky who Well Zelensky that
них вот у обоих Зели кто Ну Зеленский то
is they  both
есть они оба
there And why what's the
там А почему в чём
joke
прикол
Well well also as a politician he's not very good and what
Ну ну тоже как политик он не очень а что
bad
он тебе плохого
did he do to you Well I think he could have let's
сделал Ну я считаю что он мог давность
say at the negotiating table let's say
допустим за стол переговоров допустим
everything with Putin because there are a lot of
всё с путином потому что вот много
victims now And what not And what kind of look
сейчас жертв А что не А какие смотри
question question  in order to sit down at the
вопрос вопрос в том чтобы сесть за стол
negotiating table it is necessary What are we
переговоров нужно О чём
negotiating about Zelensky should sit down
переговаривается Зеленский должен сесть
for negotiations with Putin and accept
на переговоры с Путиным и принять
Putin's demand to give part of Ukraine to
требование Путина отдать часть Украины
Putin
Путину
Well, in essence, well, in essence Well,
Так ну он по сути же ну по сути Так ну
or let's say Putin would set the
или допустим вот Путин поставил бы
conditions not to join NATO in essence  this
условия не вступать в НАТО по сути это
is why the conflict
из-за этого конфликт
started again no no not because of
начался ещё раз ещё раз нет нет не из-за
this look let's take it that is it
этого смотри давай возьмём То есть
turns out that Zelensky in your eyes
получается зеленскому в твоих глазах
needs to sit down at the negotiating table and decide
нужно сесть за стол переговоров и решить
how much territory to give to Putin so in
сколько территорий отдать Путину так в
this there should be talk essentially yes but the
этом говоры должны быть по сути да но
territory  it won't be comparable to
территория это не будет сравнима с
human casualties let's say it's better to
человеческими жертвами допустим лучше
give up territory than to lose
отдать территорию чем потерять ещё вот
a few more Well, I think so, that is,
несколько Ну так я думаю да то есть
Putin, look, Putin cares about human
Путину смотри Путину важны человеческие
lives or not, he cares about them too Well,
жизни или нет ему тоже важны на Ну то
maybe, well, look It was logical for
может ну так смотри Логично было чтобы
Putin to give Ukraine Crimea Donetsk Lugansk
Путин отдал Украине Крым Донецк Луганск
Bryansk region Kursk and Voronezh
брянскую область курскую и воронежскую
and also part of Krasnodar Well, in order to
ещё и часть Краснодар Ну чтобы чтобы
save lives
сберечь жизнь
no, this will not happen Putin What does he want,
нет этого не будет Путин Он же что хочет
in essence, to slightly push back the
по сути чтобы чуть-чуть отодвинуть вот
borders of NATO, from the very territory,
границы НАТО вот от лише жаи территории
right, but here, look the other way around The fact is
правильно а тут смотри наоборот Дело в
that there was a buffer  zone just
том что что была буферная зона просто
this buffer zone needs to be made not on the
эту буферную зону нужно сделать не на
territory of Ukraine on the territory of Russia
территории Украины на территории России
that is look instead of
то есть смотри вместо того чтобы
pushing back the borders of NATO push back the
отодвинуть границы НАТО отодвинуть
borders of Russia Well that's logical Yes if
границы России Ну вот логично Да если
Russia doesn't want to be close to Ukraine with
Россия не хочет быть близко с Украиной с
NATO it pushes its borders beyond
НАТО она отодвигает свои границы за
the territory of Kursk region Belgorod
территорию Курской области Белгородской
Bryansk  Voronezh and Krasnodar
Брянской Воронежской и Краснодарского
regions and
края и
everything can be politics We
всё может быть ж политика Мы же всех
don't know all the details, let's say Maybe they
тонкостей не знаем допустим Может у них
have something in their chapter too We don't
там что-то у себя в главе тоже Мы же не
know what they think about right Well,
знаем о чём они думают правильно Ну
look, I just Zelensky
смотри я я просто вот Зеленский
suggested Zelensky suggested on the forum
предлагал Зеленский предлагал на форуме
in doos Yes the formula of peace Yes what if Putin
в доос Да формулу мира Да что если Путин
does not want NATO to be in the neighborhood yes it
не хочет чтобы НАТО было по соседству да
turns out Putin is withdrawing troops from
получается Путин выводит войска из
Ukraine on the territory of the Russian
Украины на территории Российской
Federation a kilometer-long demilitarized zone is being created
Федерации делается километровая
That's it
демилитаризованная зона Вот это
Belgorod Kursk region Bryansk Yes,
Белгородская Курская область Брянская Да
that's the whole ball that NATO peacekeepers are being introduced there,
вот полностью такой шар туда вводятся
uh, oh, UN Peacekeepers UN
Миротворцы НАТО ээ ой ООН Миротворцы ООН
so that there is no NATO, the UN Peacekeepers
чтобы не было НАТО онов ские Миротворцы
will patrol this kilometer-long
будут патрулировать вот эту километровой
Zone on the territory of the Russian Federation
Зону на территории Российской Федерации
Yes, so that uh, delimit Russia and NATO,
Да чтобы э разграничить Россию и НАТО
that's all And you're also from Rostov  that you are from
вот и всё А вы тоже с Ростова что вы с
Rostov, nothing, yes, from Rostov family,
Ростова да ничу а да из Ростова рода
you just have a Ukrainian accent, in
у вас просто украинский акцент у нас в
Rostov if you were with us in Rostov, in
Ростове если ты был у нас в Ростове в
Rostov and in Krasnodar, we have
Ростове и в Краснодаре у нас
Gag because Kuban
Гаг потому что Кубани
was usurious, they
ростовщическое были
migrated, I know, yes, we also had one when I
переселялись знаю да нас ещё я когда в
came to Moscow  they kept telling me
Москву приезжал постоянно мне говорили
that
что
I, in short, we are from the south,
я короче мы с юга
in short, also Belgorod, I met a guy from
короче также Белгородский мне пацан с
Belgorod, they also are [ __ ],
Белгорода встречался они тоже гэ
cabins, Wait a second, just a minute, I'm
кают Подожди секунду вот прмо минута я
going to the toilet now, okay,
сейчас туалет схожу О'кей
so here you are, you quickly put
так я тут ты что-то быстро отложил
the larva in someone, descending, but you
личинку в кого спускания а
realized, pushy, pushy  Yes, I have a
понял напористый напористый Да у меня
Bavarian beer here, I'm drinking it little by little, but have
вот стоит бавар пива потихонечку пью а
you washed your hands or not?  What did you
Руки ты помыл или нет Что руки
wash your hands No, come on, go wash my hands okay
мыл Нет давай сходи по мои руки ладно
Oh, listen, but look, what do you think
О слушай а вот смотри как ты думаешь
Posha I live in America, it's far away for me
Поша Я живу в Америке мне это ну далеко
Russia Ukraine I don't see what's
Россия Украина Я не вижу что там
really going on there In our eyes,
действительно проходит В наших глазах
here in America, yes When Russia attacked
вот тут в Америке да Когда Россия напала
Ukraine, they thought  that everything here is a couple of days
на Украину думали что тут всё пару дней
and Russia will seize everything but how is
и Россия захватит всё да как так
it that Russia still has
получается что Россия до сих пор даже от
n't really advanced much even from Donetsk I
Донецка толком не продвинулась сильно Я
don't know Well I don't
не знаю Ну я не
know but essentially what's there step He's
знаю ну по сути же что вот там шагу Он
essentially Well not a military Zhek military
же по сути Ну не военный Жек воен
[ __ ]  already long ago
дего уже давно
nezhe started let's
неже начинал
say Well and on the other
допустим Ну и с другой
hand it is much easier to defend the territory
стороны оборонять территорию намного
than
легче чем
to capture Well yes Kursk region will not
захватывать Ну да Курская область не
let you
даст со
lie in Kursk region you see Russians
врать в Курской области видишь россияне
defend
оборони
the territory And what
территорию А тебя сколько сейчас
time is it now what time is it already 9
времени-то сколько у тебя времени уже 9
am California yes it's
утра Калифорния да
normal for us morning  We are almost on the other
нормально нас утро Мы же почти на другом
side of the
конце
globe and what do
шарика а что там чем
you do there I am a teacher at the
занимаешься Я преподаватель в
university I teach anthropology who teaches
университете антропологию преподаю кого
anthropology but I don't know this one
антропологию а такой не
humanitarian
знаю гуманитарная
science Well what about the salary there is it okay to
наука Ну что по зарплате там нормально
live there in general not a very good salary I wanted
живётся не совсем хорошая зарплата хотел
more I have colleagues  which
больше у меня вот есть коллеги которые
I get more than 99,000 dollars a
больше я получаю 99.000 долларов это
month, which in Russian is somewhere around 900,000 rubles a
месяц это по-русски где-то 900.000 руб в
month, but my
месяц получается но это у меня вон
colleagues at the department get 12,000
коллеги на кафедре получают 12.000
dollars. Well, somehow I get it, its kind of
долларов Ну как-то я де получаю это как
good, but damn, for a teacher its
бы хорошее но блин для преподавателя
possible to get more. And for an apartment  that
можно больше А квартиру что и дом
you rent a house, but you don't mean you rented a
снимаешь да дом не в смысле снимал у
house, my house was on a mortgage, like, yeah, I
меня мой дом в ипотеке типа был Да я его
paid it off on IT, it's 2%, and I also had a
выплатил на ите вообще там 2% а была ещё
dacha, maybe you saw these fires in
дача может видел вот эти пожары в
California, we had them, but my dacha
Калифорнии у нас были да у меня дача
burned down, like, right A  that they compensate at
сгорела типа пря А что компенсируют там
least something there we have insurance Everything
хотя бы что-нибудь у нас страховки Всё
we are insured the house everything the insurance
мы застрахован дом всё страховая
company pays we are buying a new one
компания выплачивает мы новый покупаю
at all no problem at all clear
вообще не проблема понятно
Yes this is my mother in Rostov yes she lives she has a
Да это у меня мама в Ростове да живёт у
pension she worked her whole life as a
неё пенсия она проработала всю жизнь
doctor Well not a doctor but a nurse a
врачом Ну не врачом а медсестрой
nurse  Her
медсестрой то 18.600 у неё
salary is 18,600, that's in dollars, 180
зарплата это короче в долларах 180
dollars is a pittance,
долларов это вообще мизер
come on, pensions. That's our horror. Well, in
да ну пенсии Да это вообще ужас наш Ну в
Russia.  it's awful I can't understand Yes
России это ужас Я вот не могу понять Да
Why does Russia, having oil, gas, gold,
Почему Россия имея нефть газ золото
diamonds Yes, sell it to the whole world and people
алмазы Да продаёт его всему миру а люди
live in poverty What's
живут бедно В чём
the trick the government is not Bulk something
фишка власть не Насыпная что-что
insatiable Vla steals Lord what's so
ненасытная Вла ворует Господи что
incomprehensible that is besides this
непонятного то есть помимо ещё вот этого
That is, we still have  everything is moisture tax let's say
То есть у нас ещ всё влага нало допустим
gasoline Here you fill up there you
бензин Вот ты заправился там ты НДС
leave VAT even in Donetsk now like here is
оставил даже в Донецке сейчас типа вот
VAT there how much is 10% like for gasoline the
НДС там сколько на 10% вроде за бензин
product went to you on the receipt there is VAT
сходил продукт тебя в чеке пишет там НДС
there
там
20% here is an apartment too if
20% вот квартиру тоже вот если квартиру
you buy an apartment there is also the state every
покупаешь там тоже государство каждый
year  let's say you pay a car tax for a year,
год налог на машину допустим платишь год
sew on all sorts of food supplies, there are some in
поши на всякой завоз продуктов вот в
every country.
каждую страну
Cool. And where do young people mostly
Прикольно А куда молодёжь в основном
go from Donetsk? Well, there, to the south,
уезжает из Донецка Да ну там на юга в
mostly to
основном в
Moscow. Well, further away so that there isn't all this war there. It's
Москву Ну подальше чтобы там этой войны
damn
блин
hard there. That's it.  there is every day Here they fly T
тяжело То есть каждый день Вот летят Т
sausage Rona from Ukrainian Rona there
сосиской Роны с украинской Роны там
rocket
ракета
is terrible Between two fires
ужасно получается Между двух огней
yes yes yes Well how so zone
дадада Ну как такна зона по
essentially good I'll run further Yes Yes  let's
сути хорошо побегу дальше Дава Дава дава
find Telegram right now axis VN
най Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through srg or in your ban and very
нас через срг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show to people at times I don't
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams That's why in order for
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
us Mali operational links
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
are written right now and while there in
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegram okm video tezh tsikava and
телеграме окм видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe L
подпишись L